

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

C, C#, Java, Python, PHP, Matlab

Frameworks/Systems

Deep Learning

- TensorFlow, Keras, PyTorch

Data Science

- NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, Seaborn,

Scikit-Learn

Others

- Ruby on Rails, Laravel

COURSES

- Neural Networks and Deep Learning/ Coursera
- Al for Everyone/Coursera
- Machine Learning Crash Course/Google Developers
- Signal and Image Processing, Deep Learning/ TED University
- Database Design and Programming with SQL/ORACLE
- Machine Learning, Deep Learning/IEEE TURKEY SECTION
- Radar Systems Fundamentals/ASELSAN
- DATAI TEAM
 - Statistics & Python: Basic Statistics Science
 - Deep Learning and Python: Deep Learning
 - Machine Learning and Python
 - Data Visualization
 - -Data Science and Python: Expertise

CONTACT

+90 544 416 35 35

■ elif.meseci@outlook.com

in linkedin.com/in/elifmeseci/

github.com/elifmeseci

kaggle.com/elifmeseci

REFERENCES

Assist. Prof. Dr. Caner OZCAN CEO, Founder of SimurgAl

+90 (370) 418 7050

ELIF MESECI

Computer Engineer

PERSONAL PROFILE

I completed my bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering Department at Karabuk University. I have been working as an Artificial Intelligence Developer at SimurgAI. I started my master's degree in Computer Engineering Department at Karabuk University. I have a researcher, harmonious personality with strong problem-solving skills and high communication skills.

EDUCATION

KARABUK UNIVERSITY

Master of Science in Computer Engineering | 2021 -

KARABUK UNIVERSITY (GPA- 3.04 / 4.00)

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering | 2016 - 2021

EXPERIENCE

AI DEVELOPER

SimurgAl | Nov 2020-

 Literature review of related studies and analysis of artificial intelligence algorithms, application of deep learning techniques for image segmentation, use of artificial intelligence and machine learning solutions in solving algorithms for complex problems, evaluation and improvement of the performance of applications developed in the field of artificial intelligence.

SUMMER INTERN

Karabuk University | Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

 Data science, data analysis, machine learning and deep learning studies has been conducted

LABORATORY ASSISTANT

Karabuk University | Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

• Student Assistant of CME112-Programming Languages Course

PROJECTS

ANALYSIS OF PANORAMIC DENTAL IMAGES USING ARTIFICIAL LEARNING TECHNIQUES

SimurgAI | 2020- 2021

As the workload of dentists is too high, treatments cannot be followed regularly, and because of the COVID-19 epidemic and similar epidemic risks in the future, less doctorpatient contact is required, as a solution, artificial intelligence supported dental radiography analysis is performed.

SEGMENTATION OF BITEWING INTO ORAL X-RAY IMAGES WITH MASK R-CNN DEEP LEARNING MODEL

SimurgAI | 2020 - 2021

In the treatment and diagnosis process of teeth that need to be examined in detail in the field of dental health, bitewing intraoral radiography images are used. It is an ideal diagnostic method for the detection of recurrent caries that cannot be directly seen in the mouth, especially at the interface of small and large molars and under restorations.

CLASSIFICATION OF WRIST IMAGES WITH DEEP LEARNING MODELS

Medathon | 2021

VGG, AlexNet, ResNet were used with 1000 Hand Wrist W-Ray images submitted the under the compettion. Transfer Learning methods were used.

PAPERS

- B.Y. Tekin, C. Ozcan, A. Pekince, Y. Yasa, A. Karaoglu, S. Cilek, D. Ozdemir, E. Meseci, Tooth Detection and Numbering with Instance Segmentation in Panoramic Radiographs, International Conference on Interdisciplinary Applications of Artificial Intelligence (ICIDAAI), 1st, Online, 21-23 May, 2021.
- A. Karaoglu, C. Ozcan, A. Pekince, Y. Yasa, E. Meseci, S. Cilek, Segmentation of Bitewing Intraoral X-Ray Images with Mask R-CNN Deep Learning Model, II. International Artificial Intelligence in Health Congress 2021, SS-125,16-18 Nisan,2021.